The quality of your AI output is
determined by the quality of your input.
Most sales teams give AI generic prompts
and get generic output.
Write a follow-up email.
Summarize this call.
Draft a proposal.
The output is technically correct and
completely forgettable.
Good prompting in a sales context is
different.
It includes the buyer's specific
problem.
The language they used to describe it.
The objection they raised and the
context behind it.
The outcome they said they needed and
the timeline they gave.
When you give AI that context, the
output sounds like it was written by
someone who was in the room.
Because in a sense, it was.
Prompt engineering is not a technical
skill.
It is a sales skill.
The reps who learn it will outperform
the ones who do not.
Follow A-Gent to build it.