Territory design is one of the
highest-leverage decisions in GTM.
Most teams get it wrong.
Not because they lack data.
Because they use the wrong data.
Territories are usually built on
firmographics.
Company size.
Industry.
Geography.
These are proxies for potential.
They are not measures of it.
AI can analyze your actual win patterns.
Which account characteristics predict a
closed deal.
Which industries have the shortest sales
cycles.
Which segments have the highest
expansion revenue after the initial
close.
When you build territories on those
signals, you stop distributing accounts
evenly and start distributing
opportunity strategically.
Some reps get fewer accounts with higher
win probability.
Some get more accounts in emerging
segments worth developing.
Territory becomes a competitive
advantage, not an administrative
exercise.
Follow A-Gent to build it.