Efficiency saves time.
Leverage changes outcomes.
Most AI deployments in sales are
efficiency plays.
Summarize the call.
Draft the follow-up.
Update the CRM.
These are real gains.
But they are not the goal.
Leverage is different.
Leverage means AI is changing what is
possible, not just what is faster.
A rep who uses AI to identify the three
accounts most likely to close this
quarter is not more efficient.
They are operating with better judgment.
A manager who uses AI to see which rep
behaviors predict deal risk is not
saving time.
They are coaching with evidence instead
of instinct.
The question for every GTM leader is not
how much time did AI save this week.
The question is what decisions are we
making now that we could not make
before.
That is leverage.
That is the goal.
Follow A-Gent to build it.