Buyer evidence is not what the rep
believes.
It is what the buyer said or did.
There is a difference between a rep
saying the champion is engaged and a
buyer saying in a recorded call that
this problem is costing us two million
dollars a year and we need to fix it
before Q3.
One is an opinion.
One is evidence.
AI can help teams build an evidence
standard by surfacing what was actually
said in calls, what actions the buyer
took, what stakeholders showed up, and
what questions were asked.
When managers inspect deals using
evidence instead of rep confidence, the
pipeline becomes more accurate.
The forecast becomes more reliable.
Coaching becomes more specific.
The shift is not complicated.
It requires deciding that buyer evidence
matters more than seller optimism.
Follow A-Gent for the agent-first GTM
playbook.