If you are wondering
where to start with AI
in sales, do not start
with a giant
transformation project.
Start with one workflow:
pre-call intelligence.
Before every meaningful
sales conversation, your
team should know three
things.
First, what has changed
in this account that
could create urgency?
Second, what business
problem is likely
connected to that
change?
Third, what question
should the rep ask to
uncover whether the
problem is real?
That sounds simple.
But in most sales teams,
every rep prepares
differently.
Some research deeply.
Some skim LinkedIn.
Some wing it.
And managers only see
the damage later in the
pipeline.
An AI-assisted workflow
can standardize the
preparation without
making the conversation
robotic.
The goal is not to
script the rep.
The goal is to make sure
every rep walks in with
relevant context.
That is where AI starts
creating sales leverage.
Follow A-Gent for more
practical AI sales
workflows.