Here is the question
every B2B CEO should ask
this quarter.
Are we building an AI
tool stack, or are we
building an AI revenue
system?
A tool stack means every
team buys its own AI
point solution.
Marketing has one.
Sales has another.
RevOps has a dashboard.
Customer success has a
chatbot.
Everyone is
experimenting, but the
revenue motion does not
actually get smarter.
An AI revenue system is
different.
It connects signals,
priorities, workflows,
and decisions.
It helps the team know
who to target, what to
say, when to act, what
deal risk exists, and
where leadership
attention is needed.
That is the executive
opportunity.
Not more tools.
Better revenue
decisions.
If your AI strategy does
not improve how your
company creates,
converts, and retains
revenue, it is not a GTM
strategy yet.
Follow A-Gent if you
want to build for the
agent-first era of
sales.