Most AI sales tools fail not because the
technology is wrong but because the
workflow was never designed.
A tool gets purchased.
A demo impresses the team.
The rollout happens.
Three months later, adoption is low, the
data is inconsistent, and the team has
reverted to the old process.
The pattern repeats because the tool was
added to an existing workflow instead of
replacing a specific step in that
workflow.
Effective AI adoption requires defining
the job to be done before selecting the
tool.
What decision does this help the team
make better?
What input does it need?
What output does the team act on?
Who is responsible for reviewing it?
When that design work is done first, the
tool has a clear role.
Adoption follows because the team can
see what changes when they use it.
Follow A-Gent for the agent-first GTM
playbook.