The best AI strategy
does not automate
everything.
It defines what humans
should still decide.
In sales, AI can gather
context, detect
patterns, summarize
evidence, recommend next
steps, and flag risk.
But leadership still
needs to decide the
boundaries.
What should be
automated?
What should be assisted?
What should remain a
human judgment call
because the
relationship, nuance, or
commercial risk is too
important?
Companies that skip this
boundary design will
either underuse AI or
automate the wrong
things.
The executive job is not
simply to approve tools.
It is to design the
decision system.
Follow A-Gent for the
agent-first GTM
playbook.