AI sales adoption will
fail if managers are
left out.
Most teams focus on rep
productivity: emails,
summaries, research,
follow-up.
Useful, but incomplete.
The manager layer is
where adoption turns
into revenue impact.
Managers need AI to
surface deal risk,
compare opportunities
against buyer evidence,
identify coaching
moments, and show where
reps are skipping
critical discovery.
That does not replace
management judgment.
It improves the
information managers use
to coach.
The question is not just
how AI helps reps move
faster.
It is how AI helps
managers see reality
sooner.
That is a much bigger
revenue lever.
Follow A-Gent for more
agent-first sales
workflows.