AI can cut new rep ramp time in half.
But only if the knowledge is structured
first.
Most onboarding programs are long
because the knowledge is scattered.
Product information lives in one place.
Competitive positioning lives somewhere
else.
Objection handling is in someone's head.
Call recordings are untagged.
AI can compress the learning curve when
the knowledge is organized and
accessible.
A new rep can ask what the most common
objection is in the mid-market segment
and get a specific answer with examples.
They can review the top ten discovery
calls from the last quarter before their
first customer conversation.
They can get real-time coaching on their
first calls instead of waiting for a
weekly review.
The investment is in structuring the
knowledge before the rep arrives.
The return is a faster, more consistent
ramp.
Follow A-Gent for the agent-first GTM
playbook.