The new GTM moat is not
just data.
It is learning speed.
Every B2B company has
CRM data, marketing
data, conversation data,
product usage data, and
customer data.
The advantage is not
owning those fragments.
The advantage is turning
them into better
decisions faster.
Which accounts should we
prioritize?
Which message is
resonating?
Which deals are real?
Which customers are at
risk?
Which workflow should
change?
AI gives leaders a
chance to build a GTM
system that senses,
acts, and learns faster
than competitors.
That is the revolution.
Not artificial
intelligence as a
feature, but
intelligence as an
operating system.
Follow A-Gent for the
agent-first GTM
playbook.