The best time to surface revenue risk is
six weeks before the quarter ends, not
six days.
Most teams find out a deal is at risk
when it slips.
The rep updates the close date.
The manager asks what happened.
The answer is usually something that was
visible weeks earlier.
Stakeholder access dropped off.
Next steps went unconfirmed.
The economic buyer never engaged.
AI can surface those signals early when
it is connected to call recordings,
email activity, and CRM data.
The question is whether the team has
built the inspection habit to act on
early signals rather than wait for the
slip.
Revenue risk is not a forecasting
problem.
It is an operating rhythm problem.
Teams that use AI to inspect deals
weekly, not just at quarter end, build a
different kind of pipeline confidence.
Follow A-Gent for the agent-first GTM
playbook.