AI can help you run discovery faster.
It cannot make bad discovery good.
Discovery is broken when reps are
pitching before they understand the
problem.
When they are asking surface questions
instead of getting to economic impact.
When they are qualifying based on budget
and timeline instead of whether the
buyer has a real problem worth solving.
Adding AI to that process does not fix
it.
It accelerates it.
You get to the wrong conclusion faster.
The fix is a discovery standard.
What questions must be answered before a
deal advances?
What evidence must exist?
What does a qualified opportunity
actually look like?
Once that standard is defined, AI can
help enforce it.
It can flag calls where key questions
were not asked.
It can surface gaps in the opportunity
record.
It can prompt the rep before the next
call.
AI is a multiplier.
The quality of what it multiplies is
still a human decision.
Follow A-Gent for the agent-first GTM
playbook.