Here is the pipeline
problem no one wants to
admit.
A lot of pipeline is not
really pipeline.
It is activity with a
probability attached to
it.
The account looked
right.
The rep had a
conversation.
The opportunity was
created.
But there is no strong
buyer evidence, no clear
pain, no urgency, and no
reason to believe the
customer will change
now.
AI can help, but not if
it is only used to
summarize calls or write
follow-up emails.
The real opportunity is
to use AI to identify
missing buyer evidence
before deals become
forecast problems.
What changed in the
buyer’s business?
Who owns the problem?
What happens if they do
nothing?
What decision process
are they actually
following?
If your system cannot
answer those questions,
your forecast is still
guessing.
A-Gent helps leaders
build GTM systems around
buyer evidence, not
sales activity.