Most deal reviews are
opinion contests.
The rep says the deal is
good.
The manager pushes back.
Neither has clean
evidence.
AI changes the dynamic
when it surfaces what
the buyer actually said,
what next steps were
agreed to, what
stakeholders have gone
quiet, and what the deal
history shows about
momentum.
That is not a forecast
tool.
That is a coaching tool.
The manager stops asking
what the rep thinks and
starts asking what the
buyer evidence shows.
The conversation becomes
faster, more specific,
and more useful.
The rep learns what good
looks like.
The manager builds a
consistent inspection
standard.
That is what AI-assisted
deal review actually
delivers when it is set
up correctly.
Follow A-Gent for the
agent-first GTM
playbook.