Most B2B teams do not
have a lead problem.
They have a signal
problem.
They know which accounts
fit the ICP, but they do
not know which accounts
are showing meaningful
change right now.
That is where AI can
create leverage.
Not by blasting every
account with generic
messaging, but by
watching for shifts that
create urgency: hiring
patterns, funding
events, leadership
changes, product
launches, market
pressure, or operational
pain.
The question for sales
leaders is simple.
What signals tell us an
account may need to act
now?
If your GTM motion
cannot answer that, AI
will mostly make your
old targeting faster.
Build the signal layer
first.
Then automate the motion
around it.
Follow A-Gent for the
agent-first GTM
playbook.