Most pipeline problems start before the
first sales conversation.
The handoff between marketing and sales
is where revenue leaks.
Marketing generates a lead.
Sales receives a name and a company.
No context.
No buying signal.
No problem statement.
The rep starts from scratch.
Cold outreach to a warm contact.
AI can fix this.
Not by generating more leads.
By capturing what marketing already
knows.
Which content did this buyer engage
with.
Which pain points surfaced in their
behavior.
Which questions they asked before ever
talking to a rep.
When that context transfers to sales,
the first conversation is different.
The rep walks in knowing the problem.
Not guessing at it.
That is not a technology upgrade.
That is a revenue system upgrade.
Follow A-Gent to build it.