If your AI sales
strategy is measured by
activity volume, you may
be optimizing the wrong
thing.
More emails.
More sequences.
More call summaries.
More automated
follow-ups.
That can look productive
while making the buyer
experience worse.
The better question is
not: did AI help us do
more?
The better question is:
did AI help us act with
better timing, stronger
relevance, and clearer
buyer evidence?
Did it help us find
accounts that were
actually more likely to
move?
Did it help reps prepare
better questions?
Did it help managers see
deal risk sooner?
That is where AI creates
sales leverage.
Not by making every weak
motion faster, but by
making the right motion
easier to repeat.