Lazy personalization is
about to become obvious.
For years, teams could
pretend a first-name
token, a LinkedIn
mention, or a generic
company line was
personalization.
AI will make that easier
to produce, which means
buyers will learn to
ignore it faster.
Real relevance is
different.
It connects a meaningful
account signal to a
business problem the
buyer may actually care
about.
That is where AI can
help, but only if the
team has the right
inputs.
Better signals.
Better hypotheses.
Better timing.
Do not use AI to create
fake relevance at scale.
Use it to earn attention
with a real reason to
speak.
Follow A-Gent for the
agent-first sales
playbook.