Forecast confidence is
not the same as buyer
evidence.
A rep can feel confident
because the prospect was
friendly, the meeting
went well, or the next
step is on the calendar.
But buyer evidence is
different.
It shows that the buyer
has a real problem, a
reason to change,
internal ownership, a
decision path, and
consequences for doing
nothing.
AI can help sales
leaders make this
visible earlier.
It can inspect notes,
calls, emails, CRM
fields, and meeting
history to ask one
question: what evidence
supports this forecast?
That is a better use of
AI than another activity
summary.
Follow A-Gent for
practical AI sales
strategy.