Do not start AI sales
adoption with every
workflow at once.
Start with the first
thirty days.
Pick one revenue
problem, one team, and
one workflow.
For example: pre-call
intelligence for account
executives.
Define the signal
inputs.
Define the buyer
evidence you expect.
Define the manager
review process.
Then measure whether
calls improve, whether
discovery gets sharper,
and whether deal risk
appears earlier.
That is how AI adoption
becomes operational
instead of performative.
The goal is not to
announce a
transformation.
The goal is to prove one
workflow creates better
revenue decisions.
Then scale.
Follow A-Gent for
practical AI GTM
execution.