Single-threaded deals are the most
predictable way to lose.
One contact.
One champion.
One point of failure.
When that person goes quiet, changes
roles, or loses internal support, the
deal stalls.
AI can help identify multithreading gaps
earlier.
It surfaces which stakeholders have been
engaged, which ones have not responded,
and which roles are typically involved
in decisions at similar companies.
That gives the rep a specific reason to
reach out to a new contact rather than a
generic request to expand the
relationship.
The message becomes more relevant
because it is tied to a real gap in the
buying process.
Multithreading is not a relationship
tactic.
It is a risk management discipline.
AI makes it easier to see where the risk
is concentrated and act on it before the
deal is already in trouble.
Follow A-Gent for the agent-first GTM
playbook.