The job of the sales
leader is changing.
For years, sales
leadership was built
around activity,
coaching, pipeline
inspection, and forecast
judgment.
Those still matter.
But in the agent-first
GTM era, the sales
leader has a new
responsibility:
designing the
intelligence system
around the team.
What signals should the
team see?
What buyer evidence
should every opportunity
contain?
Where should AI support
reps, managers, and
operations?
What decisions should be
automated, assisted, or
left human?
That is the leadership
work.
Not simply approving AI
tools.
Not just encouraging
reps to experiment.
But deciding how the
revenue system should
sense, prioritize, act,
and learn.
The best sales leaders
will not become less
human because of AI.
They will become more
focused on the human
decisions that matter
most.
Follow A-Gent for the
agent-first GTM
playbook.